<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Avoid</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use">
        Terms of use:\n
By using the Avoid application (this application), you agree to the below terms of use.
All uses of \"We\", \"we\" and \"our\" in the terms of use refers to the Avoid Team (developers at DeezAppsInc).\n\n

Not Medical Advice:\n
The Avoid app is not attempting to give any form of medical advice, and is not to be substituted for, or used against the advice of a doctor.\n\n

Responsibilities:\n
We are not responsible for incorrect or missing allergens and ingredients, when scanning a product, or ever.

Avoid is developed using the Open Food Facts API that is editable by anyone, and so we ALWAYS advise reading the label of a product even if no breach in dietary
or allergy requirement is detected.

Neither the Avoid team, nor Open Food Facts take responsibility for any breach in diet preference, or reaction to any product scanned by the Avoid app.\n\n

Storing your data:\n
By creating an account, you agree for your email, as well as your dietary requirements to be stored on our Google FireBase database.
We take no responsibility for others accessing your account if you fail to keep your login details private.\n\n

Changes to terms of use:\n
The above terms of use may be changed at any time, any change to these Terms of Use will be effective as soon as they are posted.
By continuing to use the app after these changes you are showing your acceptance of these changed Terms of Use.
    </string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">
        This section informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and sharing of personal data when you sign up for, and use the "Avoid" application.\n\n
        Personal data we collect includes your email address, and associated with that email address are the individual ingredients and diet presets you have selected while using the app.
    </string>
    <string name="about_us">The Avoid app was developed in order to help those with dietary requirements speed up shopping. Especially for diets like veganism, that have hundreds of ingredients to remember to avoid!</string>
</resources>
